Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series C: Group Portraits, September 1937-August 1938.
  - Photo Unit #: C265 Nurses of 15th Brigade, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1000)
  - Photo Unit #: C266 Ambulance drivers [of the 15th Brigade in front of Illinois State International Labor Defense ambulance] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1937-12 (Box 6, Folder 11-1889)
  - Photo Unit #: C267 Doctors of the 15th Brigade [in front of Artists Union ambulance] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1937-12 (Box 6, Folder 11-1890)
  - Photo Unit #: C268 Doctor Edward Barsky and Doctor [?], 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1001)
  - Photo Unit #: C269 Lumbermen from Northwest: John Givulinovich and Wilfred "Idaho" Chapin, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1002)
  - Photo Unit #: C270 English kitchen at Alcaniz, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1003)
  - Photo Unit #: C276 Group of Servicio Sanidad [Health] of Lincoln-Washington, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1004)
  - Photo Unit #: C277 [?] and Harry Noble, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1005)
  - Photo Unit #: C279 Sound truck, R. Karman [?] and C. Silverman [?], 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1006)
  - Photo Unit #: C281 Nathan Weisenfeld [alias Neil Wesson], Major Robert Merriman, Captain Alfredo Balsa, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1328)
  - Photo Unit #: C285 Train group going from Ambite to Alcaniz, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0774)
  - Photo Unit #: C287 Train group going from Ambite to Alcaniz, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0775)
  - Photo Unit #: C288 Chauffeurs, 15th British [?], Auto Park, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1007)
  - Photo Unit #: C289 Three Carbonell brothers, Pablo, Victor, Jorge, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1008)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/23)
  - Photo Unit #: C290 Chauffeurs, "Dusty" Miller, Kaye Alexander, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1009)
  - Photo Unit #: C293 Louis Secundy, Abraham Lewis, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1010)
  - Photo Unit #: C298 John Gates (l.), Political Commissar, International Brigade base, Captain Robert Thompson, MacKenzie-Papineau and David Doran, Political Commissar, 15th Brigade, Ambite, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0776)
  - Photo Unit #: C299 David Doran, Lieutenant Harry Poll, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, General Walter [alias of Karol Swierczewski], 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0777)
  - Photo Unit #: C303 Louis Secundy, Chief of Auto Park, 15th International Brigade, 1937-12 (Box 2, Folder 11-0778)
  - Photo Unit #: C304 [?], Joe Taylor and [?], Brigade Scouts, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1329)
  - Photo Unit #: C306 At Argente, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1011)
  - Photo Unit #: C307 [?], [?] and Claude Pringle, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1012)
  - Photo Unit #: C310 Group of Brigade Commissariat, Argente, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1013)
  - Photo Unit #: C317 At front, E. [?] Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1014)
  - Photo Unit #: C319 At Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Teruel Front, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1015)
  - Photo Unit #: C320 At MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion near [?], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1016)
  - Photo Unit #: C327 Cubans in the 24th Brigade, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1017)
  - Photo Unit #: C330 Couriers of 15th Brigade, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1018)
  - Photo Unit #: C331 Motor cyclists of 15th Brigade, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1019)
  - Photo Unit #: C333 Jesse Wallach, Samuel Romer, Eugene Nolte of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1020)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C337 In Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0779)
  - Photo Unit #: C338 In Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0780)
  - Photo Unit #: C345 Robert Merriman, Earl Browder, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0781)
  - Photo Unit #: C346 Earl Browder, Vladimir Copic, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0782)
  - Photo Unit #: C348 Earl Browder and officers of the 15th International Brigade, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0783)
  - Photo Unit #: C349? Earl Browder and officers of the 15th International Brigade, 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1875A)
  - Photo Unit #: C350 Earl Browder[center] and officers of the 15th International Brigade, 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1865)
  - Photo Unit #: C351 William Oderaka, Robert Minor, Anthony Drossel, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0784)
  - Photo Unit #: C354 Edward Barsky (l.) and Edward Patterson, MacKenzie-Papineau, after Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0785)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/2)
  - Photo Unit #: C355 On the anniversary of their last year in Spain, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0786)
  - Photo Unit #: C357 After Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0787)
  - Photo Unit #: C358 Morris Stamm (l.) and [?], Lincoln-Washington, after Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0788)
  - Photo Unit #: C360 Group of Californians in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Agua-viva [?], 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1021)
  - Photo Unit #: C363 Lillian Armstan, nurse, and Norman Dorland, 35th Division Sanidad [Health], 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1022)
  - Photo Unit #: C365 Scene in front of Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Cedrilla, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1023)
  - Photo Unit #: C366 Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1024)
  - Photo Unit #: C367 Kitchen, Lincoln-Washington, 1938-02 (Box 1, Folder 11-0378)
  - Photo Unit #: C368 Eating at Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1025)
  - Photo Unit #: C369 Lincoln-Washington Battalion eating, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1026)
  - Photo Unit #: C370 Lincoln-Washington Battalion eating, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1027)
  - Photo Unit #: C371 Paul White of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1028)
  - Photo Unit #: C372 Soldiers of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1029)
  - Photo Unit #: C373 John Panaszewicz of Lincoln-Washington fortification group, John P. Hunter of Lincoln-Washington Chemical Unit, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1030)
  - Photo Unit #: C374 Anthony Kerhlicker, Elias (Ilya) Balagurchick, Lincoln-Washington fortification, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1031)
  - Photo Unit #: C380 Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Valverde, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1032)
  - Photo Unit #: C384 South American of Company 2, 59th Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1033)
  - Photo Unit #: C385 Machine-Gun group of Company 2, 59th Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1034)
  - Photo Unit #: C386 Machine-Gun group of Company 2, 59th Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1035)
  - Photo Unit #: C388 Cubans in 59th Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1036)
  - Photo Unit #: C393 Dr. Imek Bernstein, Maxim. Lieutenant [?] Biegelman, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1037)
  - Photo Unit #: C394 Captain Leonard Lamb, Lieutenant William Digges, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1038)
  - Photo Unit #: C395 Mappers and observers of the Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1039)
  - Photo Unit #: C396 Preparing rifles for inspection, Lincoln-Washington, 1938-03 (Box 1, Folder 11-0259)
  - Photo Unit #: C397 Preparing rifles for inspection at Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1040)
  - Photo Unit #: C398 Preparing rifles for inspection at Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1041)
  - Photo Unit #: C399 Greeks in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1042)
  - Photo Unit #: C400 Greek Cypriots in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1043)
  - Photo Unit #: C401 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion at Valverde, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1044)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/13)
  - Photo Unit #: C402 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion at Valverde, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1045)
  - Photo Unit #: C403 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion at Valverde, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1046)
  - Photo Unit #: C406 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Group, Valverde, 1938-03 (Box 8, Folder 11-1330)
  - Photo Unit #: C407 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Valverde [?] [soldiers on ground], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1866)
  - Photo Unit #: C409 Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1047)
  - Photo Unit #: C426 British Battalion office, Valverde; [soldier using a typewriter on the ground], 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1815)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/14)
  - Photo Unit #: C431 Air bomb holes, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1048)
  - Photo Unit #: C432 Transmissions: Harry Fellman, John Rossen and Harry Perlman, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1049)
  - Photo Unit #: C441 At work at Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Hijar, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1050)
  - Photo Unit #: C446 Printing a bulletin, political commissariat at work, Brigade mimeo (2 Spaniards) at Emilio Sanchez (17, killed Baleau) Proper spelling to come soon., 1938-03 (Box 8, Folder 11-1331)
  - Photo Unit #: C451 Brigade Runners, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1051)
  - Photo Unit #: C455 Robert Merriman, Nicolai [?], undated (Box 8, Folder 11-1332)
  - Photo Unit #: C456 Spanish cooks of MacKenzie-Papineau, Letux, 1938-03 (Box 8, Folder 11-1333)
  - Photo Unit #: C459 Wood for MacKenzie-Papineau kitchen, Letux, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1052)
  - Photo Unit #: C461 Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau, Letux [resting in a grove], 1938-03 (Box 8, Folder 11-1334)
  - Photo Unit #: C465 Office, 15th Brigade, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1053)
  - Photo Unit #: C468 Company 3 Headquarters, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1054)
  - Photo Unit #: C469 Company 4, Letux, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1055)
  - Photo Unit #: C472 Intendencia boys hauling oranges, Alcorisa, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1056)
  - Photo Unit #: C473 Group from base Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Alcorisa, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1057)
  - Photo Unit #: C475 Lieutenant Sanchez, Herman (Gabby) Klein, [?], Lieutenant [?] Carmona, Harry Lichter, Eloy Bouha [?], 1938-02 (Box 2, Folder 11-0789)
  - Photo Unit #: C484 Ambulance: [?], [?], Murray Nemeroff, Valls, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1058)
  - Photo Unit #: C487 Group of 15th International Brigade Sanidad [Health], 1938-04 (Box 2, Folder 11-0790)
  - Photo Unit #: C489 Officers of 15th International Brigade Sanidad [Health], 1938-04 (Box 2, Folder 11-0791)
  - Photo Unit #: C493 Runners and Transmiciones [Transmissions], Ulldemolins, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1059)
  - Photo Unit #: C494 Some of the Commissariat, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1060)
  - Photo Unit #: C496 In front of 15th Brigade in Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1061)
  - Photo Unit #: C497 Working on a car, Auto Park, Cervera, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1062)
  - Photo Unit #: C501 Civilians and Paul Meleschuk of Auto Park, Cervera, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1063)
  - Photo Unit #: C504 15th International Brigade sound truck, Codo, 1938-08 (Box 8, Folder 11-1335)
  - Photo Unit #: C507 Major Germina Galleani, Bill Parker [?], Vincent Usera, Alcorisa, 1938-01 (Box 2, Folder 11-0792)
  - Photo Unit #: C513 Juventud Socialista Unificada Members, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Ebro Front, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1064)
  - Photo Unit #: C519 Negro Machine-Gunner crew, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1065)
  - Photo Unit #: C520 Anti-aircraft unit, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1066)
  - Photo Unit #: C522 Harry Dobson, Enrique Baseto, James Bourne, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1067)
  - Photo Unit #: C523 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1068)
  - Photo Unit #: C524 Auto Park, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1069)
  - Photo Unit #: C526 Milton Wolff, [?], George Watt, [?], Lincoln-Washington, 1938-06 (Box 2, Folder 11-0793)
  - Photo Unit #: C527 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-06 (Box 2, Folder 11-0794)
  - Photo Unit #: C528 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-06 (Box 2, Folder 11-0795)
  - Photo Unit #: C529 Joseph Brandt and Captain Milton Wolff, Lincoln-Washington, 1938-06 (Box 2, Folder 11-0796)
  - Photo Unit #: C530 George Watt, Milton Wolff, Joseph Brandt, [?], Lincoln-Washington, 1938-06 (Box 1, Folder 11-0379)
  - Photo Unit #: C531 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-06 (Box 2, Folder 11-0797)
  - Photo Unit #: C532 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-06 (Box 2, Folder 11-0798)
  - Photo Unit #: C533 George Watt, Milton Wolff, Joseph Brandt, [?] Lincoln-Washington, 1938-06 (Box 2, Folder 11-0799)
  - Photo Unit #: C539 15th International Brigade Transmiciones [Transmissions], Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1070)
  - Photo Unit #: C541 15th International Brigade Transmiciones [Transmissions], wall newspaper, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1071)
  - Photo Unit #: C542 Sergants of 59th Battalion, Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1072)
  - Photo Unit #: C546 Cubans in 59th Battalion, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1073)
  - Photo Unit #: C547 First aid man of Lincoln-Washington Battalion at work Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1074)
  - Photo Unit #: C548 Group from base Auto Park, Alcover, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1075)
  - Photo Unit #: C553 15th International Brigade Observers, Ebro Front (Ivor Hickman, British Battalion, 3rd from right, kneeling and holding pole), 1938-08 (Box 3, Folder 11-1076)
  - Photo Unit #: C554 15th International Brigade observers, Ebro Front, 1938-08 (Box 3, Folder 11-1077)
  - Photo Unit #: C555 15th International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters] officers, 1938-08 (Box 3, Folder 11-1078)
  - Photo Unit #: C556 James Bourne, Langston Hughes and [?], 1937-01 (Box 2, Folder 11-0800)
  - Photo Unit #: C558 Martin Grumet, David Doran, undated (Box 8, Folder 11-1336)
  - Photo Unit #: C564 [Group of men, some in costume], undated (Box 8, Folder 11-1337)
- Series D: Miscellaneous, September 1937-June 1938; August 1938
  Series IID: Miscellaneous, September 1937 - June 1938; August 1938. The 249 images in this series include scenes of the Brigade in battlefields and at rest. Notable images include rustic cane shelters built by the Lincoln Battalion in an olive grove in Almuchel; Fascists taken prisoner at Belchite; the troops on a train from Quinto to Ambite and at a railroad station milling with civilians; soldiers in showers, washing and mending clothes, reading and playing football, and picking olives; peasants weaving; an ambulance from the Teachers Union and American Student Union with Murray Nemeroff driving; the funeral of Lieutenant William Digges at Mollerusa; the Dental Wagon with Dr. Jack Klein at work; School for Commissars at the Ebro Front; and the trial of deserters at Senes.
  - Photo Unit #: D001 Cane shelters built by Lincoln-Washington Battalion in olive grove, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0801)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/20)
  - Photo Unit #: D002 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Headquarters, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0802)
  - Photo Unit #: D004 Delousing machine, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0803)
  - Photo Unit #: D005 Murray Nemeroff and Alfred Kaufman, showers and delousing, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0804)
  - Photo Unit #: D006 Showers and delousing, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0805)
  - Photo Unit #: D007 15th International Brigade in shower machine at Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 6, Folder 11-1776)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/2)
  - Photo Unit #: D009 Showers, delousing, 1937-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-1194)
  - Photo Unit #: D011 HW Dimitroff Battalion, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0806)
  - Photo Unit #: D014 Chess, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0807)
  - Photo Unit #: D015 Hamburger Boys, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 2, Folder 11-0808)
  - Photo Unit #: D017 Vladimir Copic addressing Dimitroff Battalion prior to their leaving to join 13th International Brigade, 1937-10 (Box 2, Folder 11-0809)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/6)
  - Photo Unit #: D018 Lieutenant Colonal Vladimir Copic addressing Dimitroff Battalion prior to their leaving to join 13th, 1937-10 (Box 8, Folder 11-1338)
  - Photo Unit #: D019 Meeting of Dimitroff Battalion the night before they joined the 13th International Brigade, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 6, Folder 11-1786)
  - Photo Unit #: D023 F. O'Brien of British Battalion with Anastasia [?], son of president of CP and editor of local party paper at Modejar, Senes, 1937-10 (Box 8, Folder 11-1339)
  - Photo Unit #: D026 Presentation of awards to comrade Michael Zajac, Senes, 1937-10 (Box 2, Folder 11-0810)
  - Photo Unit #: D029 Colonel Stephen Fuqua at 15th International Brigade in Quinto (American Military Attache); Captain Hans Amlie (l.), Robert Merriman, Robert Thompson, David Doran and Colonel Fuqua, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0811)
  - Photo Unit #: D032 Colonel Stephen Fuqua and David Doran in trenches at Fuentes, Quinto, 1937-10 (Box 8, Folder 11-1340)
  - Photo Unit #: D033 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.) and David Doran in trenches at Fuentes, Quinto, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0812)
    (Moscow Number: 5/195/2)
  - Photo Unit #: D035 Street, 15th International Brigade Headquarters, Quinto, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0813)
  - Photo Unit #: D037 15th International Brigade moving pictures by Herbert Kline (probably in Quinto), October 1937. Far left, Henri Cartier-Bresson; foreground, facing camera, Jacques Lemare., 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0814)
  - Photo Unit #: D038 (During filming of) 15th International Brigade moving pictures by Herbert Kline; Herber Kline is center, with satchel over his right shoulder, back to camera., 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0815)
  - Photo Unit #: D039 Captain Hans Amlie and Colonel Stephen Fuqua, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0816)
  - Photo Unit #: D040 Colonel Stephen Fuqua and Captain Hans Amlie, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0817)
  - Photo Unit #: D041 [Filming] at Quinto: [Jaques Lemare, Henri Cartier-Bresson, and Herbert Kline], 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0818)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/23)
  - Photo Unit #: D044 Trial of deserters, Senes, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0819)
  - Photo Unit #: D050 Evacuation of civilians from Codo [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1937-09 (Box 6, Folder 11-1891)
  - Photo Unit #: D052 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.) and Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Quinto, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0820)
  - Photo Unit #: D053 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.) and Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Quinto, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0821)
  - Photo Unit #: D054 Colonel Stephen Fuqua, David Doran, and Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0822)
  - Photo Unit #: D055 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.) and Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Quinto, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0823)
  - Photo Unit #: D056 David Doran, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Colonel Stephen Fuqua, Captain Hans Amlie, Major Robert Merriman, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0824)
    (Moscow Number: 5/195/9)
  - Photo Unit #: D057 David Doran, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Colonel Stephen Fuqua, Major Robert Merriman, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0825)
  - Photo Unit #: D058 Major Robert Merriman, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Colonel Stephen Fuqua, Captain Hans Amlie, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0826)
  - Photo Unit #: D059 Trip from Quinto to Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0827)
  - Photo Unit #: D060 Lincoln-Washington kitchen on trip from Quinto to Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 8, Folder 11-1341)
  - Photo Unit #: D062 Lincoln-Washington kitchen on trip from Quinto to Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0828)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/76)
  - Photo Unit #: D063 Lincoln-Washington kitchen on trip from Quinto to Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 8, Folder 11-1342)
  - Photo Unit #: D064 Lincoln-Washington kitchen on trip from Quinto to Ambite, getting water, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0829)
  - Photo Unit #: D066 Trip from Quinto to Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0830)
  - Photo Unit #: D067 Boarding side-door Pullmans after morning coffee, Quinto-Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1768)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/72)
  - Photo Unit #: D068 Rain in camp, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-0831)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/80)
  - Photo Unit #: D069 Rain in camp, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-0832)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/77)
  - Photo Unit #: D070 Rain in camp, Almuchel, 1937-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-0833)
  - Photo Unit #: D072 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1767)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/71)
  - Photo Unit #: D073 Train at Quinto-Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1765)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/69)
  - Photo Unit #: D075 Kitchen on train, Quinto-Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1770)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/75)
  - Photo Unit #: D077 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1766)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/70)
  - Photo Unit #: D078 Train ride from Quinto to Ambite [scene of villagers and houses], 1937-11 (Box 8, Folder 11-1343)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/78)
  - Photo Unit #: D079 [?], [?] and Murray Nemeroff on train from Quinto to Abite, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0834)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/28)
  - Photo Unit #: D080 Train trip from Quinto to Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0835)
  - Photo Unit #: D081 Train trip from Quinto to Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0836)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/74)
  - Photo Unit #: D082 Quarters of English Battalion at Andujar, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1795)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/6)
  - Photo Unit #: D083 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1769)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/73)
  - Photo Unit #: D085 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite [duplicate of 11_1775], 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1772)
    Available Formats: Copy Negative; Moscownegative
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/79)
  - Photo Unit #: D085 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite [duplicate of 11_1772], 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1775)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/82)
  - Photo Unit #: D086 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite [soldiers with gear, lying on or near tracks], 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1773)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/80)
  - Photo Unit #: D088 Battalion Headquarters, Mendejar [3 men sitting on ground, reading the Daily Worker], 1937-11 (Box 8, Folder 11-1344)
  - Photo Unit #: D089 English Battalion Headquarters at Mondejar, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-1195)
  - Photo Unit #: D090 Civilians and soldiers at siding during train ride, Quinto-Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1771)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/77)
  - Photo Unit #: D091 ? with (l) Fred Mattersdorfer, (r) Einiv Junkala [Soldier playing guitar, seated in a boxcar door. Poster on exterior of car], 1937-11 (Box 8, Folder 11-1345)
  - Photo Unit #: D094 Comrades with a flag captured in Quinto, 1937-09 (Box 1, Folder 11-0260)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/13)
  - Photo Unit #: D095 [3] Lincoln Brigade members on road to Saragossa about 15 km away, undated (Box 8, Folder 11-1346)
  - Photo Unit #: D097 School in Quinto, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-1079)
  - Photo Unit #: D098 Soldiers and civilians at railroad station, train ride from Quinto-Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1774)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/81)
  - Photo Unit #: D099 Langston Hughes (l.) and Crawford Morgan [with bandaged hand] at Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-10 (Box 8, Folder 11-1347)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/19)
  - Photo Unit #: D100 Langston Hughes (l.) and Crawford Morgan at Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0837)
  - Photo Unit #: D101 Crawford Morgan (l.), [?] Markowitz, [?] Parker and Langston Hughes, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0838)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/7)
  - Photo Unit #: D102 Langston Hughes, Quinto - Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0839)
  - Photo Unit #: D104 Nurse Lillian Armstan, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0840)
  - Photo Unit #: D106 Nurse Irene Goldin, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0841)
  - Photo Unit #: D107 Fiesta in Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, [crowded street, soldiers on balcony with flag], 1937-10 (Box 6, Folder 11-1780)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/9)
  - Photo Unit #: D108 Fiesta in Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro [outdoors, crowd listening to a piano-player], 1937-10 (Box 8, Folder 11-1348)
    Available Formats: Copy NegativePrint; Moscow negative